yeah that's right I've seen Donna Kelsey
got a picture with her Ed Kelsey walked
in just a little bit ago about just over
an hour ago both of them telling me they
haven't been here since their boys were
attending school here so a very exciting
uh welcome back to UC for them and right
now hundreds if not thousands of people
are still trying to get into Fifth Third
Arena here on uc's campus uh you can see
here this is the student entrance a lot
of these um people going in now uh are
the UC students we know that they did
get uh there was a free lottery for
tickets so these students didn't have to
pay for them we know there's been a lot
of excitement people of all ages here
Joe burrow Orlando Brown Jr Bengals
players both special guests tonight uh
for this event the do opened at 5:00 so
they've been filing in for 45 minutes
and this line is still as long as I can
see the event starts at 7:00 and the
podcast won't even start recording until
9:00 and of course you know we can't
talk about Travis Kelce without Taylor
Swift being in the mix there there's
been rumors all over campus today that
Taylor Swift is going to make an we have
not been able to confirm that I have not
seen her and we saw so many people here
for so many different reasons but I
talked to some people who were here at
9:30 this morning they say they're here
for all of it you guys have been in line
since 9:00 this morning why we're just
big fans and we really wanted great
seats these Kelsey brother fans traveled
for hours and were first in line for the
taping of Kelsey's New Heights podcast
at the University of Cincinnati I see
that you have the sweatshirt why why are
you such a big fan to the Kelsey
Brothers I am a huge fan of Travis I
actually have a fan page for him on
Instagram so I'm excited to see him that
Instagram fan page just so happens to
have 164,000 followers have you ever
seen him in person I have not no I have
not Bearcat football players plan to
meet with Travis and Jason before doors
open to Fifth Third Arena I play online
so Jason going to be my favorite part of
it what does it mean to you to play on a
team that the Kel brothers played on
Amazing you know they did great things
in the league so them coming up here
just amazing you got a good feeling UC
Public Safety teamed up with several
police agencies for K9 sweeps and
traffic details but as of Thursday
afternoon they still couldn't answer one
very important question so I think what
a lot of people want to know is is
Taylor Swift coming so unfortunately I
do not know um and I I still don't know
that's an honest honest answer uh
however uh we have not been told that
that's one of the reasons for the
preparation we are preparing as if she
is going to be here however we do not
know what are you hearing about if she's
going to be here or not be here I think
it would be pretty cool if she showed up
in Cincinnati I'm going to be honest
whether you like her or you don't like
her she's huge and she makes good music
one thing is for sure Mom Donna Kelce
isn't missing it she stopped to take
pictures with fans outside a Fifth Third
Arena what are you hoping really happens
today um honestly I'm just a good time
um I'm a big fan of Taylor obviously but
a big fan of Travis and Jason a bigan
fan of sports and football in general
it's you know a big a big deal around
here and uh everybody's excited for it
and we're excited for it
so now the rain has picked up and you
can see that a lot of these people here
are you know just going through it
they've been standing in the rain many
of them for hours it's been raining off
and on throughout the afternoon and into
the evening this whole event actually
had to be moved from nippard Stadium
where they originally had planned uh to
have this into Fifth Third because of
the weather tonight all of the tickets
have been sold sure you could stop
watching now but let's be honest you
want to see more so click some of those
links are better yet go ahead and tap
subscribe that way you'll catch more
content from local 12